hey what is up guys
i just wanted to do a very quick review
of the
feiyutech
uh squirt focus
motor
uh it can either focus or it can zoom in
zoom out for you i don't know if you
guys can see that or not
um
but yeah it's it's pretty badass
so
what happens is
you put
this rubber gear
around either your focus or your zoom i
chose zoom
and then it has a brushless motor
that attaches to that
and via some
linkage
uh from right here
down to
the front
of the scorpc
it's able to control your zoom for you
and here i will show you that let me um
just power on
[Music]
and via
this uh twisty knob
i don't know what it's called exactly
but we can control
the zoom
i think it's pretty awesome
uh here it is actually working
very cool very very cool piece of
equipment um it's only about
um a hundred and twenty hundred and
thirty us dollars
but it is well worth it uh for you
um camera enthusiasts out there
um it will definitely take your game up
to the next level
the
feiyutech
scorp focus motor
i mean these guys are like light years
ahead of the game
so if you like filming
as much as i do
um
this is definitely a good option